(Howard:)Thanks for helping us sort
through all my mom's stuff.
(Raj:)Of course.
(Raj:)I know what it's like
(Raj:)having to go through
a loved one's possessions.
(Raj:)My uncle was
a worshipper of Krishna.
(Raj:)But after he died,
you know what we found?
(Raj:)A statue of Shiva.
(Raj:)It may not be
Crips and Bloods, okay?
(Raj:)But in India, it's a thing.
(Bernadette:)Well, it'll be good
that you're there.
(Bernadette:)Howard's been having
trouble deciding
(Bernadette:)what to keep
and what to let go.
(Howard:)Well, it's hard.
(Howard:)A lot of Ma's stuff
brings back fond memories.
(Bernadette:)Is that why you couldn't
get rid of
(Bernadette:)her drawer
full of ketchup packets?
(Howard:)Yes. It reminds me of us
eating out and her saying,
"Quick, nobody's looking,
fill your pockets with ketchup."
(Sheldon:)Leonard?
(Sheldon:)Have you ever noticed that